A Finding Aid to the Esta Nesbitt Papers, circa 1942-1981, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Xerography Research Files, circa 1966-1974; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 2.5 Linear feet Box 2-4, 11, OV 16
  - Xerox Brochures, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - Convenience Copier 4000, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Copier, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Drafting Printer and Practices, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Engineering Print System, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - How the Xpect Company Found Out What It Was, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Microfilm Printer, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Reduction Duplicator, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Telecopier, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Xerox Standard Equipment, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Xerox Systems Centers, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Clippings, circa 1966-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Clippings, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
    Oversized material housed in OV 16.
  - Magazines, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
    Oversized material housed in Box 11, Folder 2.
  - Notebooks, Archival Resource Key (Box 2)
    - Notebook, 1970 May-July; Archival Resource Key; "May 27/70 to July 5/70 SOME XEROX CORP. NOTES IN HERE" (Box 2, Folder 28-30)
    - Xerox "Holding-Patterns", 1970 December-1971 January; Archival Resource Key; "Xerox Book Dec 8/70 / 'XEROX' / 'HOLDING-PATTERNS'" (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Xerox Plans and Projections, 1971 January-April; Archival Resource Key; "Jan 8.1971 / XEROX Notebook / Plans & Projections / B&W Book 1" (Box 2, Folder 32-34)
    - Xerox Plans and Projections, 1971 June-October; Archival Resource Key; "June 12.71 / Xerox Notebook / Plans & Projections / Book 2" (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
    - Xerox Think-Bank Color, 1971 January; Archival Resource Key; "XEROX THINK-BANK / COLOR NOTEBOOK 1" (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Xerox Xplore 1, 1971 January-March; Archival Resource Key; "XEROX 'Xplore' Notebook #1 / January '71 to March 11.1971" (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Xerox Xplore 1, 1971 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Xerox Xplore 1, 1971 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Xerox Xplore 1, 1971 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Xerox Xplore 2, 1971 March-December; Archival Resource Key; "Xerox Xplore Notebook #2 / March 11.71 continuing" (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Xerox Xplore 2, 1971 March-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Contains material removed from notebook in Box 3, Folder 4.
    - Xerox Xplore 2, 1971 March-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Xerox Xplore 2, 1971 March-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Xerox Xplore 3 Chromacapsagraphics, 1971 December; Archival Resource Key; "Xerox Xplore / Special Notebook #3 (color transfer) chromacapsagraphics / Dec 15-1971" (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Xerox Xplore 3 Chromacapsagraphics, 1971 December; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Xerox Xplore Bibliography, 1971 July; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Xerox Xplore Chroma-Capsagraphy, 1971 May-1972 January; Archival Resource Key; "Xerox Xplore / chroma-capsagraphy / May 3.1971" (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
      Oversized material for Folder 12 housed in Box 11, Folder 3.
  - Notes, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Oversized material housed in Box 11, Folder 4.
  - Notes, 1971 July 7; 1972 April 8; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Slides and Transparencies, Archival Resource Key (Box 3)
    - Experiments and Works in Progress, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Completed Prints, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16-17)
  - Xerography Studies, 1967 June 14; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Xerography Studies 3M Preliminary Notes and Reference Materials, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19-21)
  - Xerography Studies, 1970 December 11; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Xerography Studies Xerox Process Information, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23-24)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 February 8; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 February 18; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 February 25; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 March 11; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29-30)
    Oversized material housed in Box 11, Folder 5.
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 March 25; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 April 1; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 April 8; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 April 12-22; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
    Oversized material housed in Box 11, Folder 6.
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 April 22-29; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 April 29; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 May 6; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37-39)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 June 3; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 June 17; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2-7)
    Oversized material for Folder 7 housed in Box 11, Folder 6.
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 June 24; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 July 8; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9-12)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 July 22; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 July 29; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 September 9; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
  - Xerography Studies "Book of the Elevens", 1971 September 9; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Xerography Studies Self Portraits, 1971 September 9; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Xerography Studies Book VI, 1971 September 16; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Xerography Studies for Extensions Show, 1971 November 30; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 20-21)
  - Xerography Studies "The Horse's Dream", 1972 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Oversized material housed in Box 11, Folder 7.
  - Xerography Studies, 1972 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Xerography Studies "Map of Mind", 1972 April 16; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Xerography Studies, 1972 May 25; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Xerography Studies, 1971 June 3; 1972 August–November; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Xerography Studies, 1972 November 14; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 27-28)
    Oversized material housed in Box 11, Folder 8.
  - Xerography Studies, 1974 February 26; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Oversized Magazines, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Oversized material from Box 2, Folder 27.
  - Oversized Notebook, Xerox Xplore Chroma-Capsagraphy, 1971 May-1972 January; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Oversized material from Box 3, Folder 12.
  - Oversized Notes, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Oversized material from Box 3, Folder 13.
  - Oversized Notes, 1972 April 8; 1971 July 7; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Oversized material from Box 3, Folder 14.
  - Oversized Xerography Studies, 1971 March 11; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Oversized material from Box 3, Folders 29 and 30.
  - Oversized Xerography Studies, 1971 April 12-22; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Oversized material from Box 3, Folder 34.
  - Oversized Xerography Studies, 1971 June 17; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Oversized material from Box 4, Folder 7.
  - Oversized Xerography Studies, 1971 June 3; 1972 August–November; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Oversized material from Box 4, Folder 26.
  - Oversized Xerography Studies, 1972 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Oversized material from Box 4, Folder 22.
  - Oversized Xerography Studies, 1972 November 14; Archival Resource Key (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Oversized material from Box 4, Folders 27 and 28.
  - Oversized Clippings, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box OV 16)
    Oversized material from Box 2, Folder 26.
- Project and Exhibition Files, circa 1966-1981; Series 5; Archival Resource Key; 5.2 Linear feet Box 4-8, 11, 13, OV 17-19, 21, FC 22-23
  Series is arranged alphabetically by project or exhibition and then by format. Most of the film reels are arranged numerically, based on Nesbitt's notations.
  Additional documents related to the projects and exhibitions documented in this series can be found in the Correspondence, Writings, Xerography Research Files, and Printed Material series. Documentation about an anti-war exhibit at Parsons School of Design is found in the Biographical Materials series.
  The Projects and Exhibitions series contains a variety of materials related to Nesbitt's books, exhibitions, films, performance and participatory art, and other projects. The bulk of material in the series documents Nesbitt's major multimedia works, and her Xerography and Shadow Paintings exhibitions. Types of documentation are listed under the project or exhibition title, and include correspondence, annotated clippings, microfilm, notes, sketches and diagrams, tape transcripts, motion picture film, sound recordings, photographs, publicity, and source material.
  The piece Walk up-Tape on is documented with notes, photographs, and xerography. The one reel of microfilm contains documentation mostly related to Walk up-Tape on. Many, but not all, of the documents reproduced in the microfilm are found in the collection.
  Nesbitt's film and sound performance piece titled "Everyman as Anyman, or Putting On, On, On, On, On," was a multichannel projection of silent, super 8 mm films projected with as many as five stationary and moving film projectors alongside multilayered sound recordings. The motion picture film and sound recordings consist of 26 reels of Super 8 film and four sound tape reels. 23 of the film reels are numbered and one is labeled simply "GOD;" note that there is no reel 2 in the collection and the reel labeled GOD has two duplicate reels. Visual content is a wide array of abstract imagery, text, solid color frames, artwork, and split screen imagery, and ranges from three to five second shots to much longer shots. The sound track contains electronic music and spoken word recordings. Sound track reels consist of three reels of preliminary recordings and one master reel, which contains elements of the preliminary recordings compiled onto a single 2-channel track. Additional details about the content of the film and sound reels can be found in the notebooks for this project, and details about how the reels were projected for various performances are found in the notebook labeled "Everyman Projections." Source material for "Everyman" consists of words written on a variety of material, including paper towels, toilet paper, index cards, and foam boards.
  The film "Light Times 499," created with Anibal Ambert, consists of a sequence of xerographic prints from Nesbitt's serial work of the same title. Film and sound recordings consist of two reels of 16mm film and one sound cassette. One of the film reels contains splices, and the other appears to be a print of the spliced film. The cassette is labeled "preliminary soundtrack."
  The series also contains documentation about the film "Folding/Struck," but not the film itself.
  Various materials related to exhibitions document the creation of works through the installation of exhibition to the exhibition itself. Exhibitions of Nesbitt's xerography work include "Electrostatic Structures: 'New Morphs,'" "Electroworks," "Esta Nesbitt: Xerography Prints," and "Xerography --Extensions in Art." Other exhibitions include the participatory exhibition "1000 Empty 49.3 Grams: A participatory environment" and Nesbitt's exhibition of Shadow Paintings.
  Other projects documented in this series include a book entitled Poems of War and Revolution, a manuscript entitled "Sea of Movement," and an illustrated journal entitled "Shadow and Pathways."
  - "Annual New England Exhibition" at Silvermine Guild (between 1966-1969), Contact Sheets, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - "Electrostatic Structures: 'New Morphs'" (1972-1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Contact Sheets of Exhibit, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Photographs of Exhibit, circa 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Photographs of Source Material, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Press Material, circa 1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Price List and Labels for Artwork, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Slides of Exhibit, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Xerography of Eyes, circa 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - "Electroworks" at George Eastman House (1979-1981), Loan Agreement and Press Material, Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - "Esta Nesbitt: Xerography Prints" (1976), Photographs of Exhibit, circa 1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - "Everyman as Anyman, or Putting On, On, On, On, On", Archival Resource Key (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Film Announcement, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Notebook, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key; "Silver book - June '69" (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Oversized material housed in OV 17.
    - Notebook of Everyman Projections, 1969; Archival Resource Key; Transcribed from notebook cover: "'Everyman' projections - from July 8 - 1969 -" (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Notebook regarding Soundtrack, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key; "Sound Track Notes / Everyman" (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Notebook regarding Soundtrack and Film Reel Information, 1969; Archival Resource Key; Transcribed from notebook cover: "Film Everyman Notes continued: soundtrack & Burnt Zeroxes / Spring 69 / Intermedia / Film Sequences for editing" (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Photographic Material, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
      Oversized material for Folder 3 housed in OV 17.
    - Project Statement, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Soundtrack, Preliminary Recordings, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 3 Sound tape reels (Box 6, Folder 5-7)
    - Soundtrack, Master, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Source Material, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9-20)
      Oversized material for Folder 9 housed in OV 18. Oversized material for Folders 13 and 14 housed in OV 17.
    - Source Material (continued), circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 1, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 28)
      Note on film box: Reel #1 Mar 21/69. On other side of film box: #1. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #1 Mar 21/69 (4 of 24) Digitized 2014/16949 4.42. Head leader: Reel 1 Mar 28/69 Everyman as Anyman/nutty on on on on. Nesbitt Assoc. LTD Huemark 4/17/96 #5533.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 2, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 29)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyman #3 Mar 21/69. On other side of film box: Mar 21.69 #3. Note on film can: Everyman #3 Mar 21/69 (2 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/ 16949 4.41. Head leader: Reel 3 Mar 21/69 Everyman as Anyman/putting on on on on Reel #3.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 3, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 30)
      Note on film box: Everyman #4 Mar 21/69. Other side of film box: #4 Mar 21.69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #4 Mar 21/69 (3 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 4.42. Head leader: Reel #4 Everyman Mar 21/69 Everyman as Anyman/Putting on on on on Reel 4. Tail leader: Reel - 4 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 4, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 31)
      Note on film box: Everyman #5 Mar 21/69. Other side of film box: #5 Mar 21/69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #5 Mar 21/69 (4 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 4.42. Head leader: Reel #5 3/21/69 Everyman as Anyman/Putting on on on on Reel 5. Tail leader: Reel - 5 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 5, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 32)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyman #6. Other side of film box: #6 Mar 21/69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #6 Mar 21/69 (5 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 4.42. Head leader: Reel #6 Everyman as Anyman/Putting on on on on #6 March/21/69 Reel 6 and 7 should go together #6. Tail leader: Reel - 6 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 6, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 33)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyman #7. Other side of film box: #7 Mar 21/69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #7 Mar 21/69 (6 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.1. Head leader: #7 Mar 21/69 Everyman as Anyman/putting on on on on. Tail leader: Reel - 7 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 7, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 34)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyman #8. On other side: #8 Mar 21/65. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #8 Mar 21/69 (7 of 24) Digitizied 2014/16949 5.2. Head leader: 3/21/69 Everyman as Anyman/pulling on on on on Reel #8.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 8, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 35)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyone #9. Other side of film box: #9 Mar 21/69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #9 Mar 21/69 (8 of 24) Digitizied 2014/16949 5.2. Head leader: #9 Mar 21/69 Everyman As Anyman/Putting on on on on Reel 9. Tail leader: Reel - 9 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 9, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 36)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyman #10. Other side on film box: #10 Mar 21/69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #10 Mar 21/69 (9 of 24) Digitizied 2014/16949 5.3. Head leader: #10 Eeryman as Anyman/Putting on on on on #10 Mar 21/69. Tail leader: Reel - 10 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 10, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 37)
      Note on film box: # 11. On other side of film box: keep w. no #11 Mar 21/69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #11 Mar 21/69 (10 of 24) Digitizied 2014/16949 5.3. Head leader: Reel #11 Mar 21/69 Everyman as Anyman putting on on on on #11. Tail leader: Huemark 4-17-69 #5553 - Tail - 1 - Nesbitt Assoc. LTD - Reel - 11 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 11, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 38)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyman #12. On the other side of film box: Keep w 11. #12 Mar 21/69. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #12 Keep w #11 Mar 21/69 (11 of 24) Digitizied 2014/16949 5.4. Head leader: #12 Mar 21/69 Everyman as Anyman or putting on on on on #12. Tail leader: Reel - 12 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 12, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 39)
      Note on film box: Everyman as Anyman #13 (title again) Mar 21/69. Other side of film box: Everyman #13 Pink title collage w. letterhead red/acetate etched. Blue writing on plantubry. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #13 (Titles again) Mar 25/69 (12 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.4 Head leader: #13 Mar 25 Everyman as Anyman/Putting on on on on. #13. Tail leader: Reel - 13 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 13, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 40)
      Note on film box: #14 color tests and words like slids! Other side of film box: Color tests L4. Note on plastic film box: #14 Color Tests #16 Color Tests (13 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.5 Head leader: #14 color and b+w xeroxes. Tail leader: Reel - 14 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 14, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 41)
      Note on box: #15 color tests. Other side of box: Color tests reel #15. Note on plastic film box: #15 Color Tests (14 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.5. Head leader: #15 Apr 69 color tests Everyman #15. Tail leader: Tail - Reel - 15.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 15, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 42)
      Note on box: Reel #16 Everyman IA, Color #16 IA. Other side of box: Reel#16. Note on plastic box: Everyman #16 #1A, Color Students, (15 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.6. Head leader: #16 (IA) Mar 69 Students on Everyman#16 (IA). Tail leader: Reel - 16 Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 16, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 43)
      Note on box: #17 Everyman Reel #17 #2B Color #2B Students. Other side of box: #17 #2B. Note on plastic box: Everyman #17 #2B Color Students (16 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.6 Head leader: Mar 69 #17 (2 B) Student in Everyman #17 2 B. Tail leader: Reel - 17 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 17, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 44)
      Note on box: Everyman #18 #3C Students. Other side of box: #18 3C. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #18 #3c Students (17 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.7 Head leader:#18 3C Mar 69 Students on Everyman #18 3C. Tail leader: Reel - 18 - Tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 18, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 45)
      Note on film box: #19 B+W film from notebook. Everyman #19 B+W. Other side of film box: #19 B+W film. Note on plastic film box: Everyman #19 B+W film from notebook (18 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.7. Note included with film: I didn't make duplicates of these! EN. Leader: #19 B+W Everyman from Notebook. Small piece of film: handwritting on notebook paper with red number 17 over handwritting.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 19, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 46)
      Note on film box: Film Students #20 Work for Parsons. Other side of film box: Students Work reel #20. Note on plastic film box: #20 #4D Film of Students Work for Parsons, (19 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949. Head leader: Apr 69 Student work reel #20
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 20, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 47)
      Note on film box: #21. Other side of film box: Film of student work for Parsons Reel #21. Note on plastic film box: #21 #5E film of students for for Parsons (20 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949 5.8. Head leader: #21 Mar 69 Students #2 Reel 21. Tail leader: Reel - 21 - tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 21, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 48)
      Note on film box: #22. Other side of film box: Everyman reel #22 Burnt #A. Note on envelope:Everyman #22 Burnt #A (21 of 24 reels) Digitized 2014/16949. 5.9. Head leader: Everyman Burnt #22. Tail leader: Reel 22 tail.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 22, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 49)
      Note on film box: #23. Other side of box: Everyman reel #23 Burnt xeroxes #B. Note on preservation film container: Everyman #23 Burnt Zeroxs #B. (22 of 24 reels) Digitized 2104/16949 5.9. Head leader: Apr 69 Everyman "Burnt" Reel #23.
    - Everyman as Anyman Reel 23, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Film reel Super 8mm (Item FC 50)